Juliano Daniel Marcelino, M.Sc. System and Business Analyst

Life Philosophy

I enjoy help people (and companies) to solve problems.

Profile

Solid experience in IT and customer support, IT management, governance, consultant and teaching experience, on worldwide companies and organizations.

Hard skills includes business and systems analysis, software development, among other technologies, as well in agile methodologies and lean IT.

My main soft skills are ethics, teamwork, organization, QC-Story, communication, negotiation and flexibility.

Experience

02/13 - ongoing Uniasselvi Group

Remote and On-site postgraduate and graduate classes and mentoring thesis in technology and engineering.

SENAI/SC - Jaraguá do Sul

Remote and On-site undergraduate professor.

7707/15 - 04/19 Catholic University Center Santa Catarina Remote and On-site undergraduate professor.

17.09/12 - 12/13 Anhanguera Educational

On-site postgraduate and extension projects mentoring.

77.09/11 - 02/13 Delinea Education Technology
Remote technical writer and professor.

7 02/09 - 02/12 SENAI/SC – Jaraguá do Sul

IT and Business Management Specialist, coordinator of the computer architecture and operating systems laboratory.

FCJ – Cenecista College of Joinville Professor in Administration and Software Development.

2008 - 2009 ECEDB – Dom Bosco Educational Center Mentoring courses in IT and Administration.

17,2007 - 2008 INPG – National Postgraduate Institute
Assistant professor and tech/educational consultant.

📆 2007 - 2008 📗 Soft Expert Automation

Project manager and consultant in EDI, BPM, BSC, SWOT, KPI, KB, QA and SPLAN management systems.

7 2003 - 2006 Datasul/NeoGrid

Deployment and integration in ERP, EDI, CRM, B2B, B2C, e/c-Commerce, VMI, JIT, forecast, kanban, and SCI.



Keep in touch

@ juliano@jmarcelino.com.br

+55 (47) 99199-4901

Jaraguá do Sul - SC - Brazil

ojmarcelino

in ojmarcelino

Certifications

2021 CertiProf LGPD

Foundation (LGPDF)

2020 Kanban Institute
Kanban Foundation (KIKF)

📆 2020 🖜 CertiProf

Scrum Foundations Professional Certificate (SPFC)

2010 Cisco NetAcad

Education

7 2019 UniSociesc

Masters of Science in Production Engineering, emphasis on Lean IT.

2012 Uniasselvi

MBA in Teaching to Higher Education.

2008 INPG (pending diploma)

MBA in Project Management.

📆 2007 🔊 Univille

Bachelor in Information Systems.

Languages



Juliano Daniel Marcelino, M.Sc. Analista de Sistemas e Negócios

Filosofia de vida

Eu ajudo pessoas (e empresas) a resolver problemas.

Perfil

Sólida experiência em TI, atendimento ao cliente, gestão e governança, consultoria e docência, com experiência em organizações no mundo todo.

Hard skills incluem análise de sistemas e negócios, desenvolvimento e uso de metodologias ágeis e ferramentas baseadas em pensamento enxuto (lean thinking - lean IT).

Nas soft skills estão ética, trabalho em equipe, organização, QC/MASP, e flexibilidade em negociações e comunicação.

Experiência

📆 02/13 - atual 🔠 Grupo Uniasselvi / Kroton

Aulas presenciais e remotas em graduação e pós, além de mentoria e orientação em TCC em tecnologia e engenharia.

📆 09/19 - 02/21 📖 SENAI/SC - Jaraguá do Sul

Professor em aulas remotas e presenciais para graduação.

7/15 - 04/19 Centro Universitário Católica de Santa Catarina Professor em aulas remotas e presenciais para graduação.

📆 09/12 - 12/13 📗 Anhanguera Educacional

Professor de pós-graduação e mentoria em projetos de extensão. **Educação**

7 09/11 - 02/13 Delinea Education Technology Professor conteudista e escritor/revisor técnico.

📆 02/09 - 02/12 📖 SENAI/SC – Jaraguá do Sul

Coordenador do laboratório de arquitetura e sistemas operacionais, especialista em gestão de negócio e TI.

📆 2008 - 2009 🏢 FCJ – Faculdade Cenecista de Joinville Professor de Administração e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas.

📆 2008 - 2009 📗 CEDB – Centro Educacional Dom Bosco Professor e orientador de cursos em TI e administração.

📆 2007 - 2008 📖 INPG – Instituto Nacional de Pós-graduação Professor assistente e consultor educacional.

📆 2007 - 2008 📗 Soft Expert Automação

Gerente de projetos e consultor de EDI, BPM, BSC, SWOT, KPI, KB, QA e sistemas de gestão estratégica.

📆 2003 - 2006 📗 Datasul/NeoGrid Implantação e integração de ERP, EDI, CRM, B2B, B2C, e/c-Commerce, VMI, JIT, forecast, kanban, e SCI.



Contato

iuliano@jmarcelino.com.br

+55 (47) 99199-4901

Jaraguá do Sul - SC - Brazil

ojmarcelino

in ojmarcelino

<u>Certificações</u>

📆 2021 🖲 CertiProf LGPD

Foundation (LGPDF)

📆 2020 🖲 Kanban Institute Kanban Foundation (KIKF)

77 2020 CertiProf

Scrum Foundations Professional Certificate (SPFC)

📆 2010 🔎 Cisco Net Acad Cisco Certified Instructor

📆 2019 🔎 UniSociesc - Mestrado em Engenharia de Produção com ênfase em TI enxuta (Lean IT).

📆 2012 🔎 Uniasselvi - MBA em Docência no ensino superior.

📆 2008 🔳 INPG - MBA in Project Management. (pending diploma)

📆 2007 🖲 Univille - Bacharelado em Sistemas de Informações.

Idiomas (baseado no padrão CEFR)



en US es MX B2 B2 B1 A2 B1 pt BR Idioma Nativo Libras BR Equivalente B1-B2